There's a story behind every marriage.
A 28 year old woman and a 28 year old man
that look normal to others,
met 3 years ago
through introduction from a mutual friend.
It's time now to make decisions.
All the calculations regarding this man are over.
Timing is the only thing left now.
I decided that I want to marry the man
who is in front of me at this moment.
Can we get married?
Okay... good good.
Look this way... there we go.
Okay!
These pictures look cheap.
Is that the best you can do?
Let's do it again.
- How does the pasta taste?
- It's delicious.
- Is the pizza to your liking?
- Yes, thank you.
- How is the dessert?
- It's delicious.
- Is it good?
- We just started eating.
The bread wasn't baked long enough.
Its not crunchy enough.
How it's baked can vary.
But the dessert today is killer.
Wait for it, okay?
Here, today's highlight!
It doesn't look like
there's anything special about it.
We've had this before
and the ice cream doesn't look
like it's anything special either.
I think you were born with special skills
to bring down people.
Ki Joong... I think it would be more
helpful if you'd just leave.
I got it, good luck.
Star with the ice cream first Hae Yoon...
even though it's nothing special.
- Do you think he's upset?
- No, it's okay.
What's wrong, Hae Yoon?
Hae Yoon! Hae Yoon!
I think she's choking on the ring!
119... 119!!!
- 119... 119!
Move aside, I saw something like this on TV.
Move over!
Are you okay, Hae Yoon?
Episode 1: Women's dream proposal.
So you planned it today, didn't you?
This is the second thing I have planned. What if I ruin it again?
What are you going to do?
What do you think we're going to do?
What is there to do in a hotel?
You want to sleep with me?
With all the respect I have showed you,
I hope you make a decision too.
First let me look at the room.
I want to see just how much
you think of me.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Marry me.
Can you make me a promise?
That you'll always be honest with me?
I will always be honest with you as
I have been since the first day I met you.
This is the proposal that I've been waiting for.
Simple and without any flair.
I love you.
Let's love each other forever.
That was an expensive lamp.
I'm sorry.
I'll buy you another one.
Do you think this is something
you can buy so easily?
I'll just replace it with a same one.
Then go ahead and buy me one.
Lets see what you're capable of.
-But first, clean that up.
- I have to clean it up?
Then do I need to be the one to clean it up?
Since you're the one who broke it,
you should be the one to clean it up.
How low...
Don't act like all the other women out there.
Acting weak and defenseless...
I know you don't like that either.
- Do you even love me?
- What does love have to do with this?
It's a lamp, only a lamp.
We were about to make love..
and then the lamp falls and breaks,
then you got angry about it.
If what we were doing was more important
then you would've forgotten about the lamp.
But you are putting the lamp in first place instead of me,
that's why I'm bringing up the love thing.
Yes, if we had just started dating
of course, I would've chosen making love
to you in this situation.
But it's been over five years
since you and I have started dating.
I've made love to you countless times,
and right now,
this lamp bothers me much more
than the idea of making love to you.
Making love to you
is different than loving you.
That's just physical desire.
- Then let's get married.
- Huh? What?
We've dated over five years
and if there's no longer any meaning left to
making love, then let's just get married.
Why is marriage being brought up now?
I'm really confused.
You mention love when the lamp breaks
and you mention marriage
when we're taking about about love...
Why are you joking around with something so serious?
Ever since Jung Hoon told me that he was
proposing to Hae Yoon, I've been envious.
I want to celebrate anniversaries
just like all the other women.
and be able to lean on my man.
That means you've changed.
When you first started dating me
you told me you couldn't stand woman that depend on men.
I was wrong with the concept I chose.
Then was how you came onto me
all planned out?
Do you think that you're so great that
I would plan things out about approaching you?
I said that was my concept when I was young.
Then that means that you're old now?
You know that the more you talk,
the less appealing you're becoming?
For the first time... I'm speaking to you honestly.
The truth is, I'm fragile.
I'm not strong.
I liked you because you were strong.
But now I realize that I've been scammed.
Fragile old women don't appeal to me.
Seriously... now tears?
I guess we've reached the end of our road.
Let's take some time out to think.
Did you find this ring pretty?
Rather than it being pretty.
I heard that it's more important to pick
wedding rings that represent eternity.
I've heard that before.
You bought the ring with Dong Bi, right?
I'm really bad at it, right?
It's because it's my first time.
And who had the idea to put the ring
inside the ice cream bowl?
- Ki Joong... right?
- Should I do it again?
I don't like you being too close to Ki Joong.
How can you two be in the same family?
It's just that you two share the same genes.
Whenever I think about that,
it makes me consider you again.
You know that's not right.
He takes after his dad's side of the family,
and I take after my mon's side of the family.
That's why It's right.
Since you take after you mom a lot...
I'm sure you and Ki Joong have so much in
common since he is your mom's nephew.
I'm telling you, he has more of
the Gong family blood flowing in his veins.
Anyways, what's wrong with him?
He;s a good person.
A good person would sleep with a woman
for that long without marrying her?
You're being too harsh.
He's pretty picky about where
he makes his bed too
If Dong Bi doesn't like it,
she can just leave.
This is why I don't like you being
too close to Ki Joong.
- I don't want him to influence you.
- Am I a kid or something? Influenced?
I know what I'm doing with my life.
If you're someone who knows what he's doing
why did you put the ring in
the ice cream and almost killed me?
You always bring things up from the past
and make it difficult for me.
Make things difficult for you?
When have I made things difficult for you?
Forget it... let's not do this
We're going to ruin this happy day.
You want to stop
after getting me all riled up?
This is what you're always like,
If you start something, finish it.
Why do you always stop halfway
and slap me upside the head?
When have I ever hit you upside the head?
When have I ever made things difficult for you?
To be honest, it's true that you're pretty
ruthless about how you treat me.
And because I love you more,
I can take it and endure it.
But... I don't like the fact that it's today of all days.
Me telling you that I don't
like you being close to Ki Joong
it's just an opinion.
Alright... I know that I can't win
against you in an argument
It frustrates me to think that this is how
I going to have to live the rest of my life.
- It's still not too late
- What?
You're regretting having
proposed to me right now.
And I'm telling you that it's still not too late.
How... how can you speak like that?
You think that a marriage is a joke?
You said I frustrated you!
I just said it out of anger,
you think I was serious about that?
Words spoken rashly
are usually how you honestly feel.
I've realized clearly how you feel just now.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to go home.
- Aunt, I'm at the front of the house.
- Unie just went to bed. Come in quietly.
- Did you bring dried filefish fillet?
- Of course.
Is Hye Yoon really not coming home tonight?
You must be crazy
You drank alcohol didn't you
Seeing you makes me act like kid.
After being disappointed in love, I have no place to go but here, Aunt.
You and I, what's up with this state we're in.
Me, without a man at my age.
You, who has a man but worse off than if you didn't have one.
So let's party until we die tonight, Auntie.
What are you two doing?
What?
What are you doing with the lights off?
You weren't sleeping?
I needed to go to the bathroom so I woke up
Lately, I'm always waking up two times a night.
You should go to the hospital.
- But, you.
- Yes?
Why are you at our house?
I had something to say to auntie
I have the day off tomorrow
and I was feeling a little down, so I called her over
Start acting your age. You think you're still young?
To be hanging around girls her age? You're going to turn 60 sooner than you think
I still have 10 years left before I turn 60.
Don't talk about my age, it upsets me.
-Dong Bi, let's go in
But wait
But wait.
Wait. Weren't you with
Hye Yoon?
I got a call from her earlier saying she was going to spend the night at your place?
It wasn't me though...
It's not me, but she said she was going to a pep rally with some teachers at her school
- Really?
- Yes
Okay.. go on
Where are you right now?
What do you mean where? I'm at Tong Bin's house
Okay.
Fix that hot temper of yours
You fix it first. Then I'll fix it too. - I don't have a hot temper.
You may not have a hot temper, but you're frustrating. And you have floppy ears.
And you have floppy ears.
That's enough, it's making me feel bad
Fix that too. You should face your problems. Why avoid them?
You have a very tiring personality.
Your hot temper and how you point everything out
But you like that about me, don't you?
You're nuts about women with hot tempers that points everything out, right?
Speak, why aren't you answering when someone's asking?
I spoke. You happy?
Aren't I cool? Attractive? You've fallen for me, haven't you?
Aunt Deul Rae, let go of me.- If I let go, then I'm dead.
You lead the way
As an aunt, how can you cover up for your niece who's staying out overnight with a man?
How can you act like that when you're related to her?!
Why'd you hit me? It hurts
Where you going? - Oh it hurts
You wench's
Go and open the car door. Hurry up and get in!
Oh mom?
Come to the house tomorrow with your husband. It is a family meeting.
That Hae Yoon has finally gotten herself in trouble.
What has your husband been doing?
I told him a long time ago to find a husband for Hae Yoon.
Why hasn't been there any news?
So are you going right now to catch Hae Yoon?
Mom please don't do that. I've been through that with you too.
If you know that she's with a man, just tell her to come home immediately.
You always go out to the scene and drag us back.
Just know that it's because of what I did that you were able to become a doctor's wife!
You're talking about that again?
Alright I'll go with Tae Won's dad tomorrow.
Tae Won's Dad
Hello, this is Nam Do Hyun's plastic surgery hospital.
Madame... This is the night he works overnight.
There is a liposuction surgery and it is not over yet.
Yes, I'll contact you, yes
Does she think checking up like this is going to keep him in line?
He still does everything he wants to.
- What are you murmuring?
- There was a call from your house, director.
- She wants you to call back.
- Alright.
-Don't just say alright call her back
I got into trouble last time because
she thought that I didn't tell you about it.
Okay
Let's all go out for dinner tonight since we've worked hard today.
- Make the reservations, okay?
- Okay.
But no shots, okay?
You have a clever imagination. I am just going to eat.
I don't even know how many showers I've had today
If you didn't follow me before, you would have died in my hands.
- I like you a lot.
- I like that about you.
- Do you like this too?
- It tickles!
Does it tickle?
Hold on! Hold on!
I need to check whose calling.
Unni
Eonni (Sister/Older Sister)
What?
You are with Jung Hoon, right?
How did you know?
Mom told me
What?!
Mom's going there right now
I felt sorry so I'm telling you in advance
What's wrong?
My mom is coming.
Hurry up and get dressed before she barges in here.
So what if she come's we're getting married anyway.
My mom doesn't like you
Why?
She has very high expectations of me.
She is different from other mothers. She is very greedy.
Why didn't you tell me?
What?
That your mom doesn't like me
It would only upset you. I don't like it when you're upset.
-And I don't think my mom not liking you, is a reason for me not to marry you.
Let's hurry up and go
Let's just face her.
We have to meet anyways
Let's just face her now.
-You're saying that because you don't know her
Do you know what she was
like with my sister?
Who is it?
It's room service
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
Mom...
You're crazy
Is this how I raised you?
I raised you up with all I had without a husband.
How dare you with a married man!
I'd rather you just die instead!
Die Die
Calm down. It's all my fault mother
Why am I your mother?
Are you going to marry my daughter?
Judging from you not replying, you just played with her.
- No I did not.
-How are you going to take responsibility then?
Give me some time.
I have nothing to be scared of in the world.
There's nothing I wouldn't do for my child!
Don't think that you can just toy with her!
Just because she didn't get proper education
and there's no man in our household.
I will go to the end to destroy the bastard who hurts my child.
- I really don't know her room number.
- I'm sure she's in a suite.
Don't you think I know that girl?
She needs the best when it comes to her sleeping quarters.
- What did you say his name was?
- Who?
- Who do you think I'm talking about?
- Ha Jung Hoon.
Excuse me. I'm looking for my daughter and son-in-law but
I don't know what number room she is in
Nowadays I forget what I hear quickly.
The person's name? - Ha Jung Hoon.
If that person isn't there then, Jung Hye yoon.
They've checked out
She came today and left today?
She checked out just a moment ago.
This girl!
Will you be okay?
Are you going to be okay?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about my mother and sister.
I showed you everything that I considered embarrassing today.
Thank you
My hot temper,
When I was little, I always held it in no matter what when my mom was angry.
I got hit a lot too.
It's weird right?
When I'm around you I don't want to hold back
I'm trying to fix it.
It just means that you're that much more comfortable with me.
I'm a man who's crazy about your hot temper and about you pointing everything out.
My parents want you to come over and greet
them officially as a daughter-in-law to be.
You're driven. I like that too.
Thank you for liking it.
What should I bring when I go? I don't have anything to wear either.
- Should I buy you clothes?
- I am not asking you to buy me clothes.
I want to buy you clothes.
Let's meet tomorrow at the mall to buy clothes.
Let's go to our house
Okay, I'll call you
Don't get out of the car.
Why did you call at this time?
Ki Joong, I really feel funny.
I don't think I can home like this.
I'm against this marriage.
Hyung, you're hostile about all marriage so
your opposition doesn't count.
I can't even do this anymore. It wasn't like this during Hae Jin's time.
Why do you have to be like this? So lowly.
That's why I'm saying that you're just old in age but still a child.
What do we have?
Do we have a dependable background or money?
Fortunately since we're women, being young and pretty, we can bet on those things.
Just because you feel that way, you think that Hye Yoon will listen to you?
That's why I went chasing after her today.
How much must the man be turned off after meeting me?
Would you like this kind of mother-in-law?
Today is different than with Hae Jin.
In Hae Jin's day I went to hold onto him and today I went to break them up.
Wow the way your head works is really shocking with a capital "S".
If there is marriage there needs to be love
Love? Feed that to the dogs!
Look at me. Was I this rough from the start?
I changed to become like this because I met your brother-in-law.
That's not it. Unnie, you were originally ferocious.
Anyways, I'm not going to let my daughters' live like me
Especially Hye yoon. I've invested so much in her...
I'll make her meet a good man and fix her fate.
She more than has that right.
Don't hit my face
Are you saying that you must follow though with this wedding?
- Yes
- Aigoo who says you can?
Who told you to get married?
I love Jung Hoon.
He's never lost my trust in three years and
his sense of responsibility is strong too.
That's why I'm telling you to just date him.
Think of it as gaining experience and just date him.
and when you get married, love doesn't have much to do with it anyways.
Someone like you can marry a Doctor,
or even someone better than a Doctor!
That's your delusion.
Mom, you think that a teacher is great
but people with money don't count teachers as being anything special.
You're the one who should have more confidence.
Women teachers are first when it comes to desirable potential daughters-in-law.
And on top of that, your older sister's husband is a famous plastic surgeon in Gangnam.
And your aunt is a day care director.
They don't like girls from a single mother home
and even once the girls from such homes are married, they don't like them going home.
An old 50 year old spinster aunt isn't positive.
And on top of that Unnie's marriage isn't an honorable one.
Are you badmouthing your sister and your aunt just so that you can side with that man?
I'm not badmouthing them, I'm just telling you the reality.
Do you think I decided on my marriage using only love?
So you having done that you decide on not a large corporation
but a kid working at some small company?
Jung Hoon is someone who can accept our family's situation.
He won't betray us either.
I don't want to live my whole life being suspicious of someone, like you Mom.
Good job
Are you looking at your mother that gave birth to you with the same eyes that everyone else looks at me with?
At times, being objective is good for a relationship.
So stop criticizing Jung Hoon. I'm supposed to go give my greetings to his family tomorrow.
The wench that's supposed to be looking at things objectively
going to give her greetings first to the man's family, which country's manners is that?
If you agreed to get married of course you're supposed to go to the woman's family
first to get permission!
What big sister said is right
Then should I tell him to come tomorrow?
- Your sister is coming tomorrow.
I'm going to decide through a family meeting whether to accept him or not.
What is the family deciding on my marriage?!
If you want to do it according to your will leave and just live by yourselves, the two of you.
If you go into the marriage alone I'm sure you'll live well.
Are you cursing me right now?
This is the price for freaking me out in the middle of the night.
The earlier one was because the hand flew out due to my rude child.
Today in commemoration of Jung Hoon getting married, one shot.
How do you feel?
- About what?
What? You jerk! You're getting me all riled me up.
- Oh, Hyung. Nothing happened.
We haven't done it yet.
It's the first time I've seen someone be innocent until this age.
Is it nice to do it with a girl you love?
Nothing's happened
Oh, he's so annoying.
You're lying in case Hye Yoon embarrassed, right?
There's no innocence like that left to me now, Ki Joong.
Do you know how bitter that is?
I have no fantasy when it comes to women.
This wench or that wench, they all seem the same.
Don't curse, Hyung.
He's like that because he gets rejected all the time everyday.
When are you saying that I got rejected?!
You guys are bad.
As expected there's only Do Hyun for me.
I'd better call Do Hyun.
What hyung? - I'm lonely, come out
Who's there?
yeah
I can't come out now, I drank too much
We're going riding tomorrow. We can see each other then.
Don't be mad.
You're going riding tomorrow?
- Yeah.
Mom told us we should come because of the family meeting.
- Because of your sister's marriage?
- Mom is not satisfied with it.
Why does she not like him without even seeing him?
If it's Jung Hoon, he won't feel inferior to Sister-in-law too much.
He is better than she is.
What is wrong with Hye Yoon?
Your sister is fine, but your mother isn't.
Why, can't you come?
-Was the meeting today, I didn't know
How does somebody who is going to marry not know?
Alright let's go to the house quickly.
I'll sleep a little more because I drank before I got home.
You didn't go home but went to drink?
Are you really going to be like that?
Are you listening to what I'm saying right now?
Alright, sleep
Please break up or get married. Do one of the two.
-I'm not getting married you know-
Do you think Jung Hoon said he wants to get married because he wanted to?
I told you not to come, why did you come?
What's your reason for being like this suddenly?
You won't pick up my calls and eat alone
This is for the time we've been together
Hye Yoon.
I don't have time,
If we are going to break up, let's know the reason.
I know you didn't love me
Why, why do you think that?
It has been three years since we have met and I am 29 years old.
You know too that people are very harsh towards the age of a woman who hasn't married.
But you don't have much consideration towards a woman's age.
Is it because of how I told you that we should marry after two years?
Why can't we marry now if we can marry after two years?
Right now, it hasn't been a long time since I got my job.
I didn't have time to prepare the wedding
Either you don't love me
or even if you did love me, it is too weak.
It can't be love that passes over reality.
Then we can get married
I don't want to be bowed down to and served. You don't want to but only I want to...
I'm sorry
Should I try doing that like you did?
Do it. If he holds on, it is love.
I learned that the first time I dated.
-Sang Ji sunbae? He was really awesome
You couldn't eat for a month and you lost about five kilograms.
It is because I was traumatized on the last day.
Why did it have to be raining that night
This was it?
Was it like this?
So in the end you make your own trouble.
She was the daughter of the law firm and another lawyer
your having talked about showing your gums when you smile was because of her?
You said you didn't like her because you could see her gums.
I am going to get married.
I think you have a different fate when it comes to who you marry.
You'll meet a good man
Wipe your lips you bastard.
Hye Yoon, take the umbrella with you! If you go in this rain, you will get a cold!
I heard Sang Jin oppa is still doing well.
Why does it matter if he is doing well or not?
Why does it matter to you?
Don't be thrown away after 30 but you throw it away now.
Why do you think our interest is all on marriage?
Couldn't we be interested in something better?
Ahjumma, please give us two boiled eggs.
Yes
Good morning.
Hi... come on down.
-Wow there's no other mom like you, how'd you know I was hungover?
Now there isn't even too much time left to be here like this together.
Honey, after we get him to marry, let's go on a vacation.
Let's go on a cruise. I want to go.
Oh Mom. It's nauseating listening to your nasal voice from first thing in the morning.
She is my wife, don't talk bad about her.
Honey, when is he going to get married?
-Once you're gone we came live well
It's anger inducing, right?
Mom, don't be like that. How old are you? My Hye Yoon is so mature too.
You are taking Hye Yoon's side already.
Anyways, I won't hate Hae Yeon
Hae Yeon is coming over today right?
Nope
Why? I even did all the marketing so I could make her dinner. You can't do that.
I heard that you're supposed to go to get permission from the woman's household first?
- You are right.
- I haven't met Hye Yoon's mother.
Hye Yoon's mother wants to see me.
Then what will I do with all of the ingredients?
Honey, you have me
You should have told me yesterday.
-How could Hae yoon not tell us?
-No I just didn't tell you
You keep changing more
I am not siding with her. It is the truth.
You said Hye Yoon's elder sister's husband is a plastic surgeon, right?
-Yes
- He's Dad's college alumnus also and he knows Aunt too.
He's close to Hyung Ki Joon.
You're not going to become the unpopular one?
Doctor's aren't amazing, but there are people who think they are amazing.
Unpopular, what are you talking about?
She's not a person to discriminate based on that kind of thing.
-Why haven't you touched your rice yet?
-If I don't feed him I won't be able to eat
Still, don't do that.
He will eat if he hungry.
- Don't you dare crying!
- Stop it, he's only a child.
-If you don't like how I am acting, say something to me, not him.
I don't like your method of teaching.
Can't you raise the kid more independently?
Tae Won is a sensitive and exquisite child.
Scolding him like you is worse for him.
The rice is too sticky.
It's okay Tae Won. Let's eat.
Why are you coming back in?
Somebody has ripped the bike tires.
I have to change the entire tires themselves. I sent them out for After Service.
This is an insider's doing.
I think this is an intentional revengeful act from a grudge.
Did you do it?
- No.
- You will have to say you didn't do it.
It shows through when you lie.
Can you do things like this?
The blood in your mother's veins must flow in yours too.
Hello?
Yes mom, we were going to go right now.
Tae Won's dad said he couldn't go. He is beside me.
(mouthing "how can you tell her that I'm here?")
She told me to put you on the phone.
Hello?
Yes mother in law.
Since there is a meeting because of Hye Yoon's wedding
you must attend.
If you're the eldest son-in-law in a household with no sons don't you have to act the role of the eldest son?
Then I will see you at lunch.
You have turned your room upside down again.
What do you not like again?
After coming home from showering, I thought I should change up my room.
Write here Jung Hoon's resident registration number
and his father and mother's resident registration number.
I would know Jung Hoon's resident registration number, but how would I know his fathers?
Then find out.
- Why?
- I want to see his fate and marital compatibility.
Why do parents go into finding his fate?
Just finding his fate is not accurate. You need to put everything in.
You don't need to find out anything like that.
What has gotten you possessed?
What is your reason for marrying him?
You even went on potential marriage dates without him knowing.
Going on that blind date was something I did just for checks and balances.
It's enough that I listened to your wishes until now.
Postpone your decision to the end.
Even if you go to him, do as I tell you.
That way you will be able to be treated well in their house.
Look at your sister. She is a doctor's wife.
Mom, I don't want to live as somebody's wife but in my own name! Jeong Hye Yoon!
What a bunch of nonsense...
Just find out about the numbers and write it down!
You came?
I have given some thought about us.
Make me some bean sprouts soup.
I drank a lot last night.
Give me money so I can buy bean sprouts.
Don't you even have any money to buy some bean sprouts?
Not everyone is as rich as you are.
I didn't say anything until now
because I didn't want to seem cheap,
but there have been many times
in which I used my own money on you.
These are only the things
I've received you this past five years.
I've never once schemed anything
the whole time we were dating.
Are you really that envious of Jung Hoon and Hye Yoon getting married?
Yes I envy them.
I loved you with all my might
and you told me that you know that.
but, why are my feelings hitting a brick wall?
If you envy them, you lose.
I am no longer allowed to be used.
You're showing me the all time low yesterday and today.
You calculated when you said you loved me.
If you didn't caculated it through, a word like 'used' can't be said.
Women can't been underestimated.
Yes, you must be happy you are constantly mean.
I'm not coming to this house again, you terrible bastard, Gong Ki Joong.
Looking at how you are acting, you will be back in a week.
I bet 10 wons that you'll be back.
If you didn't have any feelings left for me, you shouldn't have come here.
You came here to tease me. You want me to hold on to you, right?
What's up, Dong Bi?
I did as you said and I got ruined.
Isn't it tiring to do that every single time you drink coffee?
Buy an espresso machine. There are $200-$300 ones.
You are saying that because you don't know this taste very well.
There's a sentiment that's felt as you make it.
What sentiment are you looking for as you make coffee?
- Why isn't your husband coming?
- He went biking.
Isn't he a crazy bastard?
He's no longer a teen, but a 40yr old man, married with a kid.
Do you want to die?
No matter what I tell him, he won't listen.
- Does he have another woman?
- What do you mean something else?
Ask him to put the house under your name.
Starts by putting all his wealth under your name one by one.
Mom, is not as if they were
having problems right now
then, why are you trying to prepare her for a divorce?
He already broken up its family once.
You don't think that he can do it twice?
What bad comes out of preparing early?
Were you surprised that I asked to see you?
No.
I didn't think this would be awkward
since we have met a few times through Ki Joon...
It is a little bit awkward.
I'm fine, Do Hyun. Please take good care of me.
I heard you wanted to get married to my sister in law.
I heard that you were dating her through Ki Joong.
I didn't know you were going to marry her.
That doesn't mean anything, but...
I thought young people nowadays dated and parted easily.
I have met Hye Yoon with a sincere heart.
Although the person directly involved is important in marriage,
the family is important too.
- Mother in law is very peculiar.
- I know.
I don't know how far and in what sister in law put it,
but you are about to shoot yourself in the foot right now.
The fact is, I'm a little bit nervous but,
you don't like me?
So is this how you are expressing your objection?
Yes, this must sound weird to you.
It must seem like I'm gossiping
about my mother in law when
you are about to join the family.
But if you still want to marry, do it.
However, I have told you early.
If it had been somebody I didn't know, I would have ignored them.
I couldn't just let it go because you are Ki Joong's little brother.
Yes, Dong Bi.
I can't go out right now.
There is a family meeting today because of Hye Yoon's marriage.
What are you doing? Do you want to come?
Since I am not family, I can't come.
Mother will say something to me.
It's alright. I'll hang up now.
Who was it to call on a day like this?
Dong Bi.
Why is she calling again?
That awful wench!
Mom don't act harshly towards Dong Bi, she is my friend, not your daughter.
She introduced Jung Hoon!
If she liked him, why didn't she date him? Why did she introduce him to you?
Mom, Dong Bi is dating somebody.
He is a man you like. He is rich and he is intelligent.
-Keeping a man like that to herself and...
But he is a confirmed bachelor..
A dummy being a dummy, right?
All the men act like that.
They have everything calculated!
Jung Hoon is a good choice for Hae Yoon.
More than anything, he's a good guy.
If anything happen, is Junh Hoo's loss.
What?
Do you know how hard it is to be normal? He is normal.
He isn't normal, aunt.
There is peace within the family.
Tae Won's dad said their family is amazing.
- They are respected as doctors too.
- What can you do with respect?
What kind of money could he have earned being a Pediatric?
No, mom. They do pretty well.
They are rich without being conceited of it.
And his father is a good man.
You can see a man's future through their father.
How does your husband know their family?
He bikes with Jung Hoon's brother.
They are crazy bastards, aren't they?
Does he ride the bike too?
I like that about him.
So, Do Hyun said all that?
Then it means he is alright.
He said so.
Then bring him home.
Fast, without wasting time!
Okay!
Does she like him that much?
Mother approved and told me you should come.
That's good.
You say it like it's other people's business.
You have a talent towards tiring people.
It is because I just came home and I am tired.
You went out? Where? Who did you meet?
- Jung Hoon.
- Mom came in my room. I'll call you later.
- Who was it?
- Hye Yoon.
She says her mom approved and I should come tomorrow.
What do you mean she approved? Where they dissatisfied with you?
It's not like that. Why are you being so sensitive?
You approved of Hye Yoon as well.
It's because I called your aunt and heard some weird things.
- About what?
- About Hye Yoon's sister.
Why?
And of top of that, I heard that she seduced
a married man to keep it by her side.
My goodness I don't even want to talk about it.
Why does aunt say such things without knowing anything?
Aren't you the one who doesn't know anything?
I heard your aunt found out not long ago.
Even if that was the truth,
what does that have to do with Hae Yoon?
It feels uncomfortable.
Even though Hye Yoon wasn't the one who had an affair with a married man?
Oh, it's disgusting.
Trust your son, mom.
You met Hye Yoon. You said she was nice.
Only trust what you saw.
You said her father was a civil servant before he passed away, right?
- What was his rank?
- Don't be like a materialistic person.
You are disappointing.
After the talking of marriage has come up, you are disappointing me.
Somebody said that a son who studies well is a country's son
and a son who earns a lot of money is mother in law's son
and a son with bad credit is my son.
But you are my mom.
You are my mom.
Why do you keep comparing yourself to Hye Yoon?
Why don't you have any confidence?
You are teasing me.
Mom.
Why did you call me out?
I hate having to go out when I'm already at home,
so why did you call me?
Am I ugly?
Did you fight with Ki Joong hyung again?
We split up.
Please do that.
He said that he will bet ‎₩10 that I will come back to him again.
Which means I am worth ten cents.
A beer, please.
What's wrong?
I don't feel well today either.
What are you doing?
Why don't I feel anything?
Why doesn't my heart flutter with just anyone?
Wow, that's low,
Seriously. Wow...
A beer, please.
What are you doing?
Jung Hoon said he would call back, but he isn't.
Then you should call him.
It would seem like I am sad.
You quibble over such little things.
What does Jung Hoon like? Unni said she needs to know so she can shop.
He likes meat. Aunt, has Dong Bi called yet?
Yes, I think something is up with her.
Why doesn't she talk about her family?
I think she doesn't have a good relationship with her father.
Her littler brother is not in Korea. She says he went to study abroad.
If they can send him to study abroad, maybe they live well.
Dong Bi says
that her father, mother and littler brother are higher class and she is of the lower class.
I think there is a secret behind her birth.
How can a girl be this heavy? You should lose weight.
Hello?
Oh really?
I split up. I split up like you said.
So you two are happy?
Who was it?
Run! This is your maximum speed?
Hey!
- Aren't you pretending to be drunk?
- No!
I feel so stuffy...
Seriously, you are so full of it.
You can't even drink, but
you always act like you can.
Go into the washroom quickly!
It is hard to get up.
When did she eat the squid?
- My stomach hurts.
- What do you want me to do about it?
Brew me some barley tea at the least.
You awful wench...
What is this all about?
My head is ringing. Open the door already!
Please stop ringing the door bell!
- Hye Yoon.
- Why are you here?
You told me you you were going to call,
but you don't even call me...
And you were here all this time?
Why is your shirt off?
My head hurts.
Put on some clothes!
Just what are you imagining right now?
What do you mean what am I imagining?
Are you crazy?
I'm sorry. You shouldn't have hugged me!
Hey! It hurts!
Seriously, it hurts!
I hit you so you would hurt. How could you push me away?
I said I made a mistake because I was surprised.
Hye Yoon, don't get married to him. If he is taken aback, he will probably hit you too.
Hey, that's not it!
No, Hye Yoon. I will never lay a hand on you.
- Even now, Dong Bi...
- Could you two please fight with your clothes on?
Aren't you guys embarrassed even with your clothes off?
Today is such a bad day.
Getting dump and make me feel suspicious
from hugging someone I feel nothing for.
I didn't suspect you of anything.
What number is this?
It's such a long number. Could it be an international call?
You make ramen.
You are going to eat again after having thrown up everything you ate?
- Are you a beast?
- If I don't do this, I can't live.
Do you guys know hardships?
Why did you call when I'm going to meet you anyways later?
Why do you ask me where is Dong Bi ?
She hasn't been picking for several days
and she hasn't been going to work. I am worried.
I was wondering if she called you.
Why would she call me if she didn't call you?
You two meet up without me knowing.
Do you know how surprised I was when I saw you two were naked?
Do you think I did it because I wanted to? It was all because of you.
Why did you make her do something like that?
What are you saying that I made her do?
There is no correct answer in a relationship.
Why did you tell her to break up with him?
You should've just left them alone to do whatever they wanted.
Then in the end, it is harder on Dong Bi's part.
You think she's having fun now?
I have to go.
I'm going to get in trouble for talking on the phone too much.
You think that you are the only person who has married?
Keep it to a minimum.
It is not good to do that at work.
-I'm sorry.
-Shut up!
Aunt, Dong Bi isn't picking up.
Can't do anything because
I have to meet Jung Hoon and bring him home
Can you go to Dong Bi's house?
Can't you leave work a little early?
Dong Bi!
I know you are in there. Open the door!
Does the pediatrician Ha Dong Gun live in this neighborhood?
Yes, he lives here. That is the house.
They have a very nice character.
And the Madame is an angel.